Cesar Rodrigo Nieto López



About me

I am a dedicated and creative programmer when implementing a solution, with extensive experience in customer service which gives me a good perspective on how to solve your doubts, with the ambition to become an essential part of where you are.

- - 443 516 5155
- **②**
 - Ampliación Solidaridad, Morelia, Michoacán
- cesar_rnl@hotmail.com
- **(**
- www.cesardev.net

Education

2007 - 2010

Cecytem cemsad 14 Capula

I had a comprehensive training, with a certificate in administrative informatics

2010 - 2013

Facultad de Ingeniería Eléctrica - UMSNH

Bachelor's degree in computer engineering up to 5 semesters with training in linux, java, data structure.

Experience

2020 - Actual

Pentafon

I work as a customer service telephone executive for an insurance campaign, in which I also work as a shift manager in the campaign.

2019 - 2020

CAPSA

He worked as a mobile application programmer in Xamarin Forms, and backend in laravel.

2019 - 2019

SUMITEL

Performed functions of branch technician performing assembly and preventive and corrective maintenance to customer equipment, in charge of the management and follow-up of product warranties and computer equipment salesman.

Technical skills

C# Xamarin Forms Angularl

Java Nodeis Ms Office

Languages

Inglés Españ

Español